<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Foodium</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="my_image_description">My Image Button</string>

    <string name="chicken_soup_description">Place a large dutch oven or pot over medium high heat and add in oil. Once oil is hot, add in garlic, onion, carrots and celery; cook for a few minutes until onion becomes translucent.\n\nNext add in grated ginger and grated turmeric. Saute for 30 seconds to let the spices cook a bit, then add in chicken broth, chicken breast, rosemary, thyme, salt and pepper.\n\nBring soup to a boil, then stir in couscous. You’ll want the chicken to be covered by the broth so make sure you stir them down to the bottom.\n\nReduce heat to medium low and simmer uncovered for 20-25 minutes or until chicken is fully cooked.</string>
    <string name="tomato_soup_description">First, prepare your vegetables. You need 1-1.25kg/2lb 4oz-2lb 12oz ripe tomatoes. If the tomatoes are on their vines, pull them off. The green stalky bits should come off at the same time, but if they do not just pull or twist them off afterwards. Throw the vines and green bits away and wash the tomatoes. Now cut each tomato into quarters and slice off any hard cores (they don not soften during cooking and you would get hard bits in the soup at the end). Peel 1 medium onion and 1 small carrot and chop them into small pieces. Chop 1 celery stick roughly the same size.</string>
    <string name="cake_description">Preheat the oven to 180°C (356°F). Grease the cake pan or line it with parchment paper. In a large mixing bowl, beat the eggs with sugar until creamy.\n\nAdd vegetable oil and milk to the egg mixture, and mix well. Sift in the flour, baking powder, and vanilla sugar. Stir until the mixture becomes smooth.\n\nPour the batter into the prepared cake pan.Bake in the preheated oven for approximately 30-40 minutes, or until a toothpick or knife inserted into the center comes out clean.Remove the cake from the oven and let it cool.Once cooled, slice the cake and serve. You can dust it with powdered sugar or drizzle chocolate sauce on top if desired.</string>
    <string name="pancake_description">In a large mixing bowl, whisk together the flour, sugar, baking powder, baking soda, and salt.\n\nIn a separate bowl, whisk together the buttermilk, milk, egg, and melted butter. Pour the wet ingredients into the dry ingredients and stir until just combined. It is okay if there are a few lumps.Heat a griddle or non-stick skillet over medium heat and lightly coat with cooking spray or butter.Pour 1/4 cup of batter onto the griddle for each pancake.Cook until bubbles form on the surface of the pancake and the edges begin to look set. \n\nThis usually takes about 2 minutes.Flip the pancake and cook for an additional 1-2 minutes, or until golden brown.Repeat with the remaining batter.</string>


</resources>